<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pantaloche</title>
    <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pantaloche</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](http://gohugo.io).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 15:51:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://inasio.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Read All the Books</title>
      <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/read-all-the-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 15:51:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inasio.github.io/post/read-all-the-books/</guid>
      <description>I like to read books. The first real books that I ever read, just lines of words in each page, were the Sandokan books by Emilio Salgari (Salgari is probably worth writing a post or two, at the very least). I read that I could find, then read them again, and then I read them again. I remember being frustrated that by chance I had managed to luck out and start reading with world&amp;rsquo;s very best most excellent books, the frustration being that it was all going to be downhill from here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta post</title>
      <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 15:35:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inasio.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new website I&amp;rsquo;m very happy to introduce my new website! The plan is to get back into writing, I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure what shape or form it will take. I remember as a kid the day that the coin dropped in my head on how writing represented spoken language, and specifically I remember that the first work I wrote (and proudly showed my mom) was meta. It&amp;rsquo;s in that sense that this is the Meta post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inasio.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;move-static-content-to-static&#34;&gt;Move static content to &lt;code&gt;static&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with &lt;code&gt;_&lt;/code&gt; will be copied as-is to the &lt;code&gt;_site&lt;/code&gt; output. Hugo keeps all static content under &lt;code&gt;static&lt;/code&gt;. You should therefore move it all there.
With Jekyll, something that looked like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is for lovers</title>
      <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/go-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inasio.github.io/post/go-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Goal
Distribute the given boxes into a hundred trucks so that the lightest and heaviest have the smallest possible weight difference.
Background
You are a great tycoon who needs to move materials, equipment and gold from Chicago to New York to build your next sky scraper. You have a convoy of 100 trucks and a variable amount of boxes to move. Unfortunately there are unscrupulous villains who would like to steal the gold from one of your shipments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo is for lovers</title>
      <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/hugo-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inasio.github.io/post/hugo-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1-install-hugo&#34;&gt;Step 1. Install Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goto &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/hugo/releases&#34;&gt;hugo releases&lt;/a&gt; and download the
appropriate version for your os and architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More complete instructions are available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://inasio.github.io/overview/installing/&#34;&gt;installing hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new theme</title>
      <link>https://inasio.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inasio.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>